#### ALEJANDRO LÓPEZ BESTEIRO

09021982

637223576 alelopbes@gmail.com www.lopezbesteiro.es

#### **PROFILE**

A multidisciplinary designer, with adaptability skills to meet the requirements of any project, whether editorial, corporate, web or mobile services. As a front-end developer, my experience includes both small-scale and large-scale projects becoming a professional adaptable to any work situation.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Graphic designer/front-end developer at Yoin

January 2012 - December 2012 (12 months)

Yoin, set up last year and currently searching for investors, aims to be a micropayment application through mobile platforms, built entirely with web language. I was part of the design group, helping to create the graphic and development material and the one in charge of the front-end of the project.

# Graphic and web designer at i2Factory (Huelva)

February 2011 - August 2011 (7 months)

My work for this technology company involves the creation of graphic, audiovisual and interactive. Taking part in projects such as the creation of a mobile application for Latin American Film Festival of Huelva.

## Advertising department (as an intern) at Onda Local de Andalucía (O.L.A) (Sevilla)

July 2010 - September 2010 (3 months)

Internship in OLA (Onda Local de Andalucía) in the advertising department performing tasks concerning the design and development of campaigns.

### Graphic designer and layout designer at Revista Sogel (Sevilla)

June 2010 - July 2010 (2 months)

I was in charge of the design and layout design of the first issue of the women's magazine "Sogel". In my internship I carried on with the task assigned previously by that magazine and finishing the entire publishing project.

## Graphic designer and layout designer (as an intern) at Revista Sogel (Sevilla)

February 2010 - April 2010 (3 months)

Internship as a designer and layout designer for the magazine "Sogel", free magazine focused on women.

# Photographer (as a intern) at EL Mundo (Huelva)

July 2009 - August 2009 (2 months)

Internship as a press photographer for El Mundo Huelva Noticias (a local newspaper).

# Photographer at Agenda Cultural Live (Sevilla)

February 2008 - April 2008 (3 months)

Co-worker photographer at this entertainment guide.

## Cameraman (as an intern) at Antena Huelva (Huelva)

April 2006 - June 2006 (3 months)

I carried out some of the practical work period of my degree at this local TV broadcasting developing camera work.

## Lighting technician (as an intern) at Proinso (Huelva)

May 2005 - June de 2005 (1 month)

Internship for the Lighting technician course. The internship took place in the entertainment company "Proinso" as part of the team in charge of the lighting.

#### **EDUCATION**

"Licenciatura en Publicidad y Relaciones Públicas" **(five-year degree in Publicity and Public relations)** by Universidad de Sevilla September 2006 - June 2011

**Certified technician in Image** /Ciclo Formativo de Grado Superior **(A higher education course)** by Instituto Pablo Neruda (Huelva) September 2004 - June 2006

**Assistant technician in Graphic design,** Curso FPO **(a course of professional training)** organized by FAECA (Seville) with a duration of 630 hours 2008

**Lighting technician**/Curso FPO **(a course of professional training)** organized by Proinso (Huelva) with a duration of 850 hours 2005

**Programmer in digital photographic report and image scanning** /Curso FPO **(a course of professional training)** organized by Ánfora Formación (Huelva) with a duration of 235 hours 2005

#### **SKILLS**

- Intermediate level of spoken and griten english.
- Driving license holder.
- Teamwork skills and ability to perform as team leader.